{
    "cards": [{
        "id": 0,
        "front": "front0",
        "back": "back0",
        "altBack": "altBack0",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 1,
        "front": "front1",
        "back": "back1",
        "altBack": "altBack1",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 2,
        "front": "front2",
        "back": "back2",
        "altBack": "altBack2",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 3,
        "front": "front3",
        "back": "back3",
        "altBack": "altBack3",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 4,
        "front": "front4",
        "back": "back4",
        "altBack": "altBack4",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 5,
        "front": "front5",
        "back": "back5",
        "altBack": "altBack5",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 6,
        "front": "front6",
        "back": "back6",
        "altBack": "altBack6",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 7,
        "front": "front7",
        "back": "back7",
        "altBack": "altBack7",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 8,
        "front": "front8",
        "back": "back8",
        "altBack": "altBack8",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 9,
        "front": "front9",
        "back": "back9",
        "altBack": "altBack9",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 10,
        "front": "front10",
        "back": "back10",
        "altBack": "altBack10",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 11,
        "front": "front11",
        "back": "back11",
        "altBack": "altBack11",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 12,
        "front": "front12",
        "back": "back12",
        "altBack": "altBack12",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 13,
        "front": "front13",
        "back": "back13",
        "altBack": "altBack13",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 14,
        "front": "front14",
        "back": "back14",
        "altBack": "altBack14",
        "hit": false
    }, {
        "id": 15,
        "front": "front15",
        "back": "back15",
        "altBack": "altBack15",
        "hit": false
    }]
}